animalhost.com 2013-09-17

# Our Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to the following website: Bestialitysection.com ("site", "we" or "us" or "our").

We respect your privacy. This policy explains how we treat information that it may obtain from you as you make use of the site. The owners and operators of Bestialitysection.com provide the site subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy. By using the site, you accept and agree to this Privacy Policy. The Privacy Policy may change from time to time, without notice other than appearing on the site. The Revision Date below will show you when the Privacy Policy was last revised.

I. This Site and Third Party Sites  
This Privacy Policy applies solely to this site. This site may contain links to third party websites that are not owned or controlled by us. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for, the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third party website. You agree that you are responsible for reviewing and understanding the privacy policies (if any) of any third party websites you may access through this site. By using this site, you release us from any and all liability arising from your use of any third party website to which this site may be linked.

II. Information Collection and Use  
A. When you visit this site, we may collect passive information about your visit. Passive information is any form of aggregate data, navigational data, tracking data, click-stream data, or historical data. It may include the domain name of your internet service provider (e.g., whether you logged on from aol.com or whitehouse.gov), referral data (e.g., the address of the last URL you visited prior to clicking through to the site) and browser and platform type (e.g., a Firefox browser on a Macintosh platform). We use this information to track how users are accessing and using the site.

B. In addition, when you visit the site we generally collect the IP Address of the computer you are using to access the Site. (An IP, or "Internet Protocol," address is a unique number associated with your computer, that may be communicated to other computers and servers when you use the Internet.) We use this information for purposes of security and anti-fraud protection.

III. Cookies  
A. This site also uses cookies and/or web beacons. (A cookie is a small amount of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive, and that may be accessed when you use a website. A web beacon is a small, transparent graphic image placed on a website, which allows the site to record the actions of a visitor opening the page that contains the beacon.)

B. We may use cookies or web beacons to: (1) determine whether visitors to the Site are unique, or whether the same user is visiting the site on multiple occassions; (2) help deliver advertisements; (3) track usage throughout the Site (e.g., tracking where traffic comes from, how traffic flows within the Site, etc.); (4) store your agreement to the terms and conditions for entering and using the Site; (5) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc.

C. These kinds of information do not, on their own, personally identify you. However, they can potentially be combined with information obtained from other sources in order to identify you. We do not ordinarily seek or obtain personally identifying information about users from others. We do reserve the right to seek such information in the event of a violation of the site Terms of Use, in the event of a dispute between this site and you, or if required by law to do so.

IV. Submitted or Posted Content  
A. We periodically allow you to submit and post audio and video content, and accompanying text ("User Content"). User Content that you submit to this site or post on the site, including any personal information included in your User Content, becomes publicly available and can be seen, collected, and used by others. You should not post any content on the site that you do not want to be seen, collected, or used by others.

B. In the process of posting User Content, you may be asked to provide some personally identifying information, such as your name and e-mail address, and other documentation. We will keep a record of the information you provide, including your personally identifiable information, and that information will be linked in our records to the User Content. We will not publically post your name or other personally identifying information, and we will not provide such information to our advertisers or business partners without your permission. However, we may disclose the personally identifying information and documentation you provide in some limited circumstances, as set forth below ("Permitted Disclosures of Personal Information").

V. Use of Visitor Information Collected by This Site  
We do not collect or share personally identifiable information about visitors to the site through the ordinary operation of the site. We may obtain and merge information about users and usage of the Site into aggregated data, which may then be used by us and/or shared with advertisers or others. When we provide aggregated information to outside companies, they will not be able to identify you or contact you based on that data.

VI. Use of Visitor Information Collected by Advertisers and Others  
We allow other companies to place advertisements on the site. These companies use technology to deliver advertisements you see on the site directly to your browser. In doing so, they may automatically receive your IP address. Other companies that place advertising on the site may have the ability to use cookies and/or web beacons to collect information, including information about your usage of the site. We do not control the processes that advertisers use to collect information. However, IP addresses, cookies and web beacons alone generally cannot be used to identify individuals, only machines. Therefore, advertisers and others whose advertisements or content may appear on the site generally will not know who you are unless you provide additional information to them, by responding to an advertisement, by entering into an agreement with them, or by some other means.

VII. Permitted Disclosures of Personal Information  
We generally do not collect personally identifiable information (data such as your name, email address, password, and the content of your communications) unless you submit User Content for posting on the site or register a user account on the site. We will not disclose any personally identifiable information it collects or obtains except: (1) as described in the site Terms of Use or this Privacy Policy; (2) after obtaining your permission to a specific use or disclosure; (3) if we are required to do so in order to comply with any valid legal process or governmental request (such as a court order, search warrant, subpoena, civil discovery request, or statutory requirement); (4) as required to protect the site's property, safety, or operations, or the property or safety of others; or (5) as otherwise required by law.

VIII. Security  
Some pages of the site may use security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of information that is transmitted through the site. However, no data transmission over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personally identifiable information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit, and you do so at your own risk.  
IX. Questions or Concerns  
If you have any questions or concerns about the site Privacy Policy, please contact by email: contact@Bestialitysection.com

This Privacy Policy was last revised on the 2nd of February 2010.
